Legends never die
All Eyez on Me is a history, drama, music film directed by Benny Boom.
All Eyez on Me chronicles the life and legacy of Tupac Shakur, including his rise to superstardom as a hip-hop artist,
actor, poet and activist, as well as his imprisonment and prolific, controversial time at Death Row Records.
Against insurmountable odds, Tupac rose to become a cultural icon whose
career and persona both continue to grow long after his passing.
Tupac Shakur, played by Demetrius Shipp Jr..
Afeni Shakur, played by Danai Gurira.
Jada Pinkett, played by Kat Graham.
Biggie Smalls, played by Jamal Woolard.
Suge Knight, played by Dominic L. Santana.
Kidada Jones, played by Annie Ilonzeh.
All Eyez on Me is a 2017 American biographical
drama film directed by Benny Boom.
Named after the 1996 studio album, it follows the life and death
of Manhattan-based hip-hop artist Tupac Shakur.
The film stars Demetrius Shipp Jr.
as Tupac, with Kat Graham, Lauren Cohan, Hill Harper, and Danai Gurira.
Jamal Woolard reprises his role as The Notorious B.I.G.
from Notorious (2009).
Talks of a Tupac biopic began in 2011 by Morgan Creek Entertainment.
The film languished in development hell for several years with various directors, including Antoine Fuqua
and John Singleton, attached at different points before Boom was confirmed in November 2015.
That December, Shipp Jr., whose father worked on music videos with Shakur, was
cast as the rapper and principal photography began that month.
It lasted until April 2016, filming in Atlanta, Las Vegas, and Los Angeles.
All Eyez on Me premiered on June 14, 2017, at the Fox Bruin Theater and was released in the
United States on June 16, 2017, on what would have been Shakur's 46th birthday.
The film was unsuccessful at the box office, grossing $55 million against a budget of
about $40–45 million, and received generally negative reviews from critics.
The tone is emotional.